TI Tok is a huge National Security
concern I can't think of a potentially
more powerful propaganda tool propaganda
tool do he just say propaganda tool I'm
sorry sir I thought the national
security threat was in terms of data
collection here are some fun facts
Instagram Facebook Google door Dash and
Airbnb all collect more data than Tik
Tok Tik Tok has contributed more than
$24 billion doll to us gross domestic
product and more than 224,000 jobs to
the US economy mind you as of January
15th the United States is over $ 36.2
trillion in debt there are over 1.3
million creators that operate their
businesses on Tik Tok in less than 24
hours 3.4 million American citizens
volunteered their data to an actual
Chinese Communist app in protests of
their own government Tik Tok is not a
publicly shared company meta is a
publicly shared company members of
Congress who voted on the Tik Tok band
are invested in meta stock meet your
politicians Senator marway Mullen
purchased between $155,000 and $50,000
of meta shares on January 2nd 20 24 on
January 26 2024 Mike McCall who
introduced the Tik Tok band legislation
was a little bit sneakier About It by
using his family's trust to purchase his
metastock representative Byron Donald
voted yay and purchased metastock on
December 6th representative Greg Stanton
voted yay and purchased metao on
November 9th 20123 representative Diana
harsh Barger voted yay and purchased
metastock on March 3rd 2023
representative Ro cona voted nay but
purchased meta stock on November 7
representative Dan crenchaw voted yay
and purchased meta stock on December 2nd
2022 representative marjerie Taylor
green vot a g and purchase meta stock on
December 30th the list goes on and on
you guys can look it up members of
Congress are actually required by law to
disclose their financial transactions
including stock trades under the stock
act ironically the purpose of that law
is to make sure that Congress members do
not make any major decisions if there's
a personal financial benefit the irony
of fear-mongering a Nation about the
threat of Chinese communism by stripping
them of their jobs Freedom of
Information freedom of speech freedom of
open communication freedom of discourse
and right to discern propaganda is wild
all while one publicly shared
corporation that is notorious for
controlling propaganda to literally
Puppeteer elections by unethically
collecting our data lobbies Congress to
vote on a ban to continue to monopolize
where we receive all of our information
and the Congress members who voted for
this Monopoly were legally allowed to
have shares in the stock but it's
totally normal the CIA lizard dump said
million into pushing this band through
because he went on Joe Rogan and talked
about jiujitsu as for me I was a broke
singer songwriter trying to make it in
the music industry and now I am one of
those 1.3 million creators that can put
food on the table because of Tik Tok it
provided me with the first equal
opportunity platform to show my songs to
the whole world I didn't need to be
Instagram famous I didn't need to be
some celebrities kid I didn't need to
have a lot of money I just needed to
post a video of myself singing to my 140
followers thanks to Tik Tok I have have
grown my audience to 14.7 million
followers I've accumulated over 270
million likes and billions of views on
my music I could sell tickets to my
shows I bought my first house from the
money I made with my Tik Tok brand
Partnerships my songs made it to top 10
radio because I promoted them on Tik Tok
I built a community of people healing
from eating disorders and with that
Community I was able to stand up to a
multi-million dollar Corporation Called
Victoria's Secret I got to sing songs
with First Responders doctors small
business owners artists kids
grandparents Olympians magicians
veterans triple amputees my Tik Tok
account was not only mine it was a place
for other people's perspectives for the
kid I babysit to confront Mean Girls in
her school it was supposed to be
something that I could show my daughter
one day and be like look Mommy made
this and you can do anything too you can
follow your dreams and you can change
the
world this just feels so icky and and
now I'm saying goodbye to the Future
that I built for my family fair and
square with a baby on the way so a bunch
of corrupt dirty politicians can feed
their
babies our greatest politicians could be
focusing on genocide poverty human
trafficking homelessness it is not about
privacy or national security it is all
about control China doesn't want to spy
on people pooping while they watch you
get ready with me the government doesn't
even hate Tik Tok in fact most of the
Congress members that voted to ban Tik
Tok are actually on Tik Tok as are all
their spouses and children what the
government hates is losing money out of
their own Pockets the government hates
losing control of the information we
receive and most importantly the
government hates when we talk to each
other